# about

My work is guided by a strong belief in design as a problem-solving tool, as a way of recognizing and forming relationships between ideas and reality, and as a method for improving the connections between people and the products they use.

I'm a visual story teller and have a passion for creating meaningful design solutions and experiences for brands and audiences. When I'm not in front of my laptop you can usually find me at café, concert or playing with fire (see skills).

# **Emily Simões**

emilysimoes.ca info@emilysimoes.ca

## **Graphic Designer**

experience

Jan 2019 - Mar 2019 / Binary Vision Studios

Redesigned company logo and created a series of logo animations. Designed social media content including Instagram posts and Facebook banners. Created visual assets and illustrations for the Binary Vision Studios website.

#### Junior Graphic Designer

Jun 2018 - Aug 2018 / Canadian Museum for Human Rights (CMHR)

Assisted in the graphic design of the Nelson Mandela exhibit. Created an icon set and UI/UX design for interactive aspects of the exhibit. Designed three unique general admission tickets.

# education

#### **Advanced Graphic Design**

Aug 2018 - Jun 2019 / Red River College

#### **Graphic Design**

Aug 2016 - Jun 2018 / Red River College

Jun 2018 - Recipient of the Terry Kuzina Memorial Student Award for Graphic Design

#### Mentorship

Aug 2018 - Jun 2019 / Canadian Museum for Human Rights (CMHR)

#### **Graphic Design Internship**

Mar 2018 / Canadian Museum for Human Rights (CMHR)

#### **Graphic Design Internship**

Dec 2017 / Investor's Group Inc.

### **Customer Service Representative**

Nov 2015 - Present / Canada's Royal Winnipeg Ballet

## skills

InDesign/ Illustrator/ Photoshop/ After Effects/ Premier Pro/ HTML/CSS/ WordPress/ Sketch/ Invision/ Photography/ Traditional & Digital Illustration/ Book Binding/ Fire Dancing

# clients

Canada's Royal Winnipeg Ballet/ Social Planning Council of Winnipeg/ Legacy Cheerleading/ Full Blüm Arts & Music Festival/ Bring Your Love Festival of Arts/ Subconscious Events/ Sloth Sounds Records